Why did the robber wash his clothes before he ran away with the loot? Answer: Because he wanted a clean getaway.																									answer
Who keeps the ocean clean? Answer: A mermaid.																									
Why did the skeleton drink eight glasses of milk a day? Answer: Because milk is good for the bones.																									
What did the snowmen eat for breakfast? Answer: Frosted Flakes.																									
Whats a baby’s favorite reptile? Answer: A rattlesnake.																									
How do you make a hotdog stand? Answer: Take away its chair.																									
Why can’t you play Hide-and-Seek with mountains? Answer: Because they're always peaking.																									
Why did Tom’s parents scream when they saw his report card? Answer: Because there was a Bee on his report card.																									
Why was the king only a foot tall? Answer: Because he was a ruler.																									
Why did Georgia’s computer keep sneezing? Answer: Because it had a virus.																									
What language does a billboard speak? Answer: Sign language.																									
What kind of tree had the best bark? Answer: A dogwood.																									
Why would the Lion not eat the Clown? Answer: Because he tasted funny.																									
What do you call a stupid doorbell? Answer: A Ding-Dong!																									
What do all students need before they get to high school? Answer: A ladder.																									
"What do you get when you cross a tuba, a drum and a spare tire? Answer: A rubber band."																									
What did the orange say to the banana when they were looking for the apple? Answer: Keep your eyes peeled.																									
Why did the golfer wear two pairs of pants? Answer: In case he got a Hole-in-One.																									
Why did the chicken cross the playground? Answer: To get to the other slide.																									
I tinted my hair and that was the highlight of my day.																									
"Two hats were hanging on a hat rack when one hat said to the other: “You say here, I’ll go on a head.”"																									
Jill went to the Emergency Room today after breaking her finger. But on the other hand she still had a great day.																									
I really wanted to fund my watch today. But I just didn't have the time.																									
Police like to interrogate drug dealers because at some point they do crack.																									
Did you hear the about the crime in the parking garage? It was wrong on so many levels.																									
The best heel thief's are hard to catch because they have good ring leaders.																									
If towels could tell jokes. They would have a pretty dry sense of humor.																									
The other day I held the door open for a clown. I thought it was a nice jester.																									
The comedian stopped at the hardware store before his performance. He was looking for new material.																									
Today I was going to tell you a joke about infinity. But it doesn't have an ending.																									
They called him the king of dentist because he specializes in crowns.																									
"When I went to the dentist to have my cavity fixed. My regular doctor wasn't there, instead there was someone else filling in."																									
1st rule of letting guest sleep in you home: if you think their terrorist don't give them the blow-up mattress.																									
I think Santa Claus moved from The North Pole to the jungles in Brazil because this year all of our presents came from Amazon.																									
"“Hey that's a cool chair.” Brendon said to Cal. “I know, it rocks!” said Cal."																									
It takes a gifted person to wrap presents.																									
I thought I would be upset when my flashlight batteries died. But instead I was de-lighted.																									
I try to talk to my parents about computer hardware but it always makes my mother-board.																									
Lumberjack love their computers. Especially when their logging in.																									
I had to buy my phone perceptions glasses after it lost its contacts.																									
Why did the capacitor kiss the diode? Because he couldn't resistor.																									
A pyrotechnics should know how fireworks.																									
Pencil sharpeners have a tough life. They live off of tips.																									
Did you hear about these new  reversible jackets? I'm excited to see how they turn out.																									
A man walked into a chimney store and asked “How much is this one?” The salesman replied: “that one's on the house.”																									
"One of my students was late to class, claiming he was in the washroom. But I think he was stalling."																									
How much does it cost to see 50 Cent featuring Nickelback in concert? Answer: 45 cents.																									
What the best part of a satellites wedding? Answer: The reception.																									
Why did Edward miss his flight out of Russia? Answer: Because he was Snowden																									
Police won't know who robbed 3M’s Scotch factory until they check the tape.																									
What happens to a frog's car when it breaks down? Answer: It gets toad away.																									
"What did the duck say when he bought lipstick? Answer: ""Put in on my bill."""																									
Can a kangaroo jump higher than the Empire State Building? Answer: Of course. The Empire State Building can't jump.																									
What do you call a pig that does karate? Answer:  A pork chop.																									
"There are five cows on a farm, one mamma cow and four baby calves. The first baby walks up to the mom and asks, ""Momma, why is my name Rose?"" The mommy cow replies, ""Well honey, a rose petal fell on your head when you were born."" The next calf comes up and asks, ""Momma, why is my name Lily?"" The mother replies, ""Because honey, a lily petal fell on your head when you were born."" The third baby comes up and asks, ""Momma, why is my name Daisy?"" The momma cow again replieds"" Well, when you were born a daisy petal fell on your head."" The final baby walks over and says, ""Duh huh guh nuh!"" The momma cow says, ""Shut up, Cinderblock."""																									
Why couldn't the leopard play hide and seek? Answer: Because he was always spotted.																									
Why did the chicken cross the playground? Answer: To get to the other slide.																									
The energizer bunny was arrested on a charge of battery.																									
"Two fish are in a tank. One turns to the other and says, ""Hey, do you know how to drive this thing?"""																									
"If you were forced to go through one of the following doors, which door do you go through with 100 % certainty you'd stay alive: a door with a man with a gun behind it, a door with a tiger who hasn't eaten in 7 years behind it, or a door with an electrical chair behind it? Answer: The one with the tiger behind it, because if it hasn't eaten in 7 years it's dead."																									
What kind of key opens a banana? Answer: A monkey.																									
What type of sandals do frogs wear? Answer: Open-toad!																									
"It was a baby mosquito's first day to fly out from home. When the mosquito came back home later that day, the father mosquito asked, ""How was your journey?"" The baby mosquito replied, ""It went great. Everyone was clapping for me!"""																									
What did the spider do on the computer? Answer: Made a website!																									
What do you call an alligator wearing a vest? Answer:  An investigator.																									
A cowboy left Montana to go to Texas on Friday and came back on Friday. How did he do it? He named his horse Friday.																									
"What did the fish say when he ran into a wall? Answer: ""Dam."""																									
What's the last thing that goes through a bug's mind as it hits your windshield? Answer: It's butt.																									
"Why does a chicken coop only have two doors? Answer: Because if it had four, it would be chicken sedan."																									
"Teacher: ""Kids, what does the chicken give you?"" Student: ""Meat!""Teacher: ""Very good! Now what does the pig give you?""Student: ""Bacon!""Teacher: ""Great! And what does the fat cow give you?""Student: ""Homework!"""																									
"A recent worldwide survey showed that out of 2,146,703,436 people, 94% were too lazy to actually read that number."																									
"A man got hit in the head with a can of Coke, but he was alright because it was a soft drink."																									
"What starts with E, ends with E, and has only 1 letter in it? Answer: An envelope."																									
"A bank robber pulls out gun points it at the teller, and says, ""Give me all the money or you're geography!"" The puzzled teller replies, ""Did you mean to say 'or you're history?'"" The robber says, ""Don't change the subject!"""																									
"What is the tallest building in the entire world? Answer: The library, because it has so many stories."																									
Why can't you trust an atom? Answer: Because they make up everything.																									
Why did the school kids eat their homework? Answer: Because their teacher told them it was a piece of cake.																									
"What did one toilet roll say to the other toilet roll? Answer: ""People keep on ripping me off!"""																									
What do you call a belt with a watch on it? Answer: A waste of time.																									
"Can February march? Answer: No, but April may."																									
"A man was walking down the street and saw a sign in a store window that said ""Help Wanted,"" so the man ran in the store and yelled out, ""What's wrong?!"""																									
What did the pop star do when he locked himself out? Answer: He sang until he found the right key!																									
Why didn't the sailors play cards? Answer: Because the captain was on the deck.																									
Why shouldn't you write with a broken pencil? Answer: Because it’s pointless!																									
Why are fish easy to weigh? Answer: Because they have their own scales.																									
Why is a baseball game a good place to go on a hot day? Answer:  Because there are lots of fans.																									
I'm thinking of becoming a hitman... I heard they make a killing.																									
"A man is filling up his car tank with gasoline and accidentally gets some on his hand. He doesn't notice it, so when he gets into his car he lights a cigarette. His arm instantly catches on fire. The man sticks his arm out the window and begins to wave it around attempting to blow out the flames crawling up his sleeve. A policeman sees the man struggling with his arm on fire and arrests him on the spot for an unlicensed firearm."																									
"Jim, Scott and Alex are tired after traveling all day and check into a hotel. When they get to reception, they find out they'll have to walk 75 flights of stairs to get to their room because the elevator is out of order. Jim suggests that they do something interesting to pass time while they walk the 75 flights. Jim will tell jokes, Scott will sing songs, and Alex will tell sad stories. So Jim tells jokes for 25 flights, Scott sings songs for 25 flights and Alex tells sad stories for 24 flights. When they reach the 75th floor, Alex tells his saddest story of all, ""Guys, I left our room key at reception."""																									
Who earns a living by driving his customers away? Answer: A taxi driver.																									
Why are ghosts such good cheerleaders? Answer: Because they have a lot of spirit!																									
What do you call security guards working outside Samsung shops? Answer: Guardians of the Galaxy.																									
Why did the tofu cross the road? Answer: To prove he wasn't chicken.																									
Why do anime fans listen to the radio in the morning? Answer: Because they enjoy car-toons!																									
Why is the letter B very cool? Answer: Because it's sitting in the AC.																									
"If a plane crashed on the Canadian/United States border, where would the survivors be buried? Answer: You don't bury the survivors."																									
Being an astronaut is funny. It's the only job where you get fired before you start work.																									
Why did the toilet paper roll down the hill? Answer: To get to the bottom.																									
"What starts with a P, ends with an E, and has a 1,000 letters? Answer: Post office."																									
"After the  smog in Los Angeles disappears, what happens? Answer: UCLA."																									
Why did Cinderella get kicked off the soccer team? Answer:  Because she ran away from the ball.																									
What did the math book say to its therapist? Answer: I've got a lot of problems.																									
What did one toilet say to the other toilet? Answer: You look a bit flushed.																									
"What did one streetlight say to the other? Answer: ""Don't look, I'm changing."""																									
A man lives and works in the same building. Every day he takes the elevator from the 10th floor down to the 1st floor where he works. At the end of the day he rides from the 1st floor up to the 7th floor and takes the stairs the rest of the way. Why? He is a dwarf and can't reach the 10th floor button.																									
"What did the magnet say to the other magnet? Answer: ""I find you very attractive!"""																									
Why do the French eat snails? Answer: They don't like fast food.																									
"What did the grape say when it was stepped on? Answer: Nothing, it just let out a little wine."																									
"Waiter: ""Do you want any dessert?"" Teddy Bear: ""No Thanks. I'm Stuffed!"""																									
Why isn't the turkey hungry at Thanksgiving? Answer: Because he's already stuffed!																									
What do get if you cross a Snowman with a Vampire? Answer: Frostbite.																									
Why are ghosts such good cheerleaders? Answer: Because they have a lot of spirit!																									
"Girlfriend: ""Am I pretty or ugly?"" Boyfriend: ""You're both."" Girlfriend: ""What do you mean?"" Boyfriend: ""You're pretty ugly."""																									
"10 Facts About You: 1. You're reading this now. 2. You're realizing that this is a stupid fact. 4. You didn't notice I skipped number 3. 5. You're checking now. 6. You're smiling. 7. You're still reading this even though it is stupid. 9. You didn't realize I skipped number 8. 10.You're checking again and smiling because you fell for it again. 11. You're enjoying this. 12. You didn't realize I said 10 facts not 12."																									
"Teacher: ""If I gave you 2 cats and another 2 cats and another 2, how many would you have?""Johnny: ""Seven."" Teacher: ""No, listen carefully... If I gave you two cats, and another two cats and another two, how many would you have?"" Johnny: ""Seven."" Teacher: ""Let me put it to you differently. If I gave you two apples, and another two apples and another two, how many would you have?""Johnny: ""Six.""Teacher: ""Good. Now if I gave you two cats, and another two cats and another two, how many would you have?"" Johnny: ""Seven!"" Teacher: ""Johnny, where in the heck do you get seven from?!"" Johnny: ""Because I've already got a freaking cat!"""																									
"Student: ""Should I get in trouble for something I didn't do?"" Teacher: ""No."" Student: ""Good, because I didn't do my homework."""																									
"Helen Keller walks into a bar, then a table, then a chair."																									
"Innkeeper: ""The room is $15 a night. It's $5 if you make your own bed."" Guest: ""I'll make my own bed."" Innkeeper: ""Good. I'll get you some nails and wood."""																									
Why are ghosts bad liars? Answer: You can see right through them.																									
"How I learned to mind my own business: I was walking past the mental hospital the other day, and I could hear all the patients shouting, ""13! 13! 13!"" The fence was too high to see over, but I saw a little gap in the planks, so I looked through to see what was going on. Someone poked me in the eye with a stick! Then they all started shouting, ""14! 14! 14!"""																									
What does a skeleton order at a restaurant? Answer: Spare ribs!																									
How do you make holy water? Answer: Boil the hell out of it.																									
"At a wedding party recently, someone yelled, ""All the married men, please stand next to the one person who has made your life worth living!"" The bartender was crushed to death."																									
Why did the fish blush? Answer: Because it saw the ocean's bottom.																									
"The past, present, and future walked into a bar. It was tense."																									
"What did the judge say when a skunk walked into the courtroom? Answer: ""Odor in the court!"""																									
Why is a river rich? Answer: Because it has two banks.																									
Why don't cannibals eat comedians? Answer: They taste funny.																									
"Police arrested two kids yesterday, one was drinking battery acid, the other was eating fireworks. They charged one, and let the other one off."																									
Have you ever tried eating a clock? It's very time consuming.																									
"I left my Adderall in my Ford Fiesta, now it’s a Ford Focus."																									
"A man was involved in an auto accident. A policeman ran up to the car and asked, ""Are you seriously injured?"" The man said, ""How should I know? I'm a doctor not a lawyer."""																									
What's a shark's favorite sandwich? Answer: Peanut butter and jellyfish!																									
"A man got in a car accident with a dwarf, who got out of his car and said, ""I'm not happy!"" The man replied, ""Well, which one are you?"""																									
"A guy walks into a bar with a piece of asphalt under his arm. He asks the bartender for a beer, and one for the road."																									
"What did the astronaut say when he wanted to be alone? Answer: ""Give me some space!"""																									
What did the zero say to the eight? Answer: I like your belt!																									
"A small boy swallowed some coins and was taken to a hospital. When his grandmother telephoned to ask how he was, the nurse said, ""No change yet."""																									
Why did the painting go to jail? Answer: It was framed.																									
"Can a match box? Answer: No, but a tin can."																									
Why did Mickey Mouse get shot? Answer: Because Donald ducked!																									
"What did the triangle say to the circle?Answer: ""You're pointless!"""																									
"Two hydrogen atoms walk into a bar. The first says to the second, ""I think I've lost an electron."" The second replies, ""Are you sure?"" to which the first retorts, ""Yes, I'm positive."""																									
Why did the reporter rush into the ice cream shop? Answer: He was looking for a scoop.																									
"There was a man who sent ten different puns to his friends, in hope that at least one of the puns would make them laugh. Unfortunately, no pun in ten did."																									
"A biologist, a chemist, and a statistician are out hunting. The biologist shoots at a deer and misses five feet to the left. The chemist takes a shot and misses five feet to the right. The statistician yells, ""We got 'em!”"																									
Why couldn't the kids see the pirate movie? Answer: Because it was rateted Rrrrr.																									
"What did the blanket say to the bed? Answer: ""I got you covered."""																									
"Two factory workers are talking. The woman says, ""I can make the boss give me the day off."" The man replies, ""And how would you do that?"" The woman says, ""Just wait and see."" She then hangs upside down from the ceiling. The boss comes in and says, ""What are you doing?"" The woman replies, ""I'm a light bulb."" The boss then says, ""You've been working so much that you've gone crazy. I think you need to take the day off."" The man starts to follow her and the boss says, ""Where are you going?"" The man says, ""I'm going home, too. I can't work in the dark."""																									
"A thief stuck a pistol in a man's ribs and said, ""Give me your money."" The gentleman, shocked by the sudden attack, said, ""You cannot do this, I'm a congressman!"" The thief replied, ""In that case, give me MY money!"""																									
Why did the can crusher quit his job? Answer: Because it was soda pressing.																									
What do your boss and a slinky have in common? Answer: They’re both fun to watch tumble down the stairs.																									
"If an accountant's spouse cannot sleep, what is the best cure? Answer: Ask the accountant to talk about their work."																									
Do you know what happens if you piss of a pilot? Answer: He takes off. 																									
Politicians and diapers have one thing in common: they should both be changed regularly… and for the same reason. 																									
Why is Peter Pan always flying? Answer: Because he neverlands.																									
Why do Batman and Robin not go fishing? Answer: Because Robin eats all the worms.																									
Why did Mickey Mouse go to space? Answer: To visit Pluto.																									
"I asked my three year old grandson Malachi what his name was, he replied, ""Spiderman."" I said, ""Malachi, what is your real name?"" He replied, ""Peter Parker."""																									
How do you wake up Lady Gaga? Poke'r Face.																									
How did the frog die? Answer: He Kermit suicide.																									
What is the difference between the American flag and American Idol? Answer: The American flag actually has stars.																									
"What's the difference between Michael Jackson and a plastic bag? Answer: One is pale, dangerous to children, and made of plastic. The other one is a plastic Bag."																									
How do astronomers organize a party? Answer: They planet.																									
Why are atoms Catholic? Answer: Because they have mass.																									
"A photon walks into a hotel. The desk clerk says, ""Welcome to our hotel. Can we help you with your luggage?"" The photon says, ""No thanks, I'm traveling light."""																									
"What did the 30 degree angle say to the 90 degree angle? Answer: ""You think you're always right!"""																									
What do computers eat for a snack? Answer: Microchips! 																									
What computer sings the best? Answer: A Dell.																									
"How many light bulbs does it take to change a light bulb? They can't, they're not bright enough."																									
"I never wanted to believe that my Dad was stealing from his job as a road worker. But when I got home, all the signs were there."																									
What do you call a bear with no teeth? Answer: A gummy bear.																									
Did you hear about the kidnapping at school? It's okay. He woke up.																									
Why does Humpty Dumpty love autumn? Because Humpty Dumpty had a great fall.																									
Did you hear about the guy whose whole left side was cut off? He's all right now.																									
"I was wondering why the ball kept getting bigger and bigger, and then it hit me."																									
"If you ever get cold, just stand in the corner of a room for a while. They're normally around 90 degrees."																									
How do trees access the internet? Answer: They log in.																									
How come oysters never donate to charity? Answer: Because they are shellfish.																									
What nails do carpenters hate to hit? Answer: Fingernails.																									
"What's the difference between a guitar and a fish? Answer:  You can tune a guitar, but you can't tuna fish."																									
Why did the scarecrow get promoted? Because he was outstanding in his field.																									
"What is the difference between a teacher and a train? One says, ""Spit out your gum,"" and the other says, ""Choo choo choo!"""																									
What kind of car does Jesus drive? Answer:  A Christler.																									
Why did the can crusher quit his job? Answer: Because it was soda pressing.																									
What type of sandals do frogs wear? Answer: Open-toad!																									
Why is Peter Pan always flying? Answer: Because he neverlands.																									
Why did the tomato turn red? Answer: Because he saw the salad dressing!																									
"On the first day of school, the teacher asked a student, ""What are your parents' names?"" The student replied, ""My father's name is Laughing and my mother's name is Smiling."" The teacher said, ""Are you kidding?"" The student said, ""No, Kidding is my brother. I am Joking."""																									
What do you get when you cross a fish and an elephant? Answer: Swimming trunks.																									
Why did the apple run away? Answer: Because the banana split!																									
What do cars eat on their toast? Answer: Traffic jam.																									
Why did the man take toilet paper to the party? Answer: Because he was a party pooper.																									
A naked man broke into a church. The police chased him around and finally caught him by the organ.																									
How can you get four suits for a dollar? Answer: Buy a deck of cards.																									
Why did the coach go back to the bank? Answer: To get his quarterback!																									
"A neutron walks into a bar and says, ""I'd like a beer. How much will that be?"" The bartender responds, ""For you? No charge!"""																									
Why are hairdressers never late for work? Answer: Because they know all the short cuts!																									
How do birds fly? Answer: They just wing it!																									
What's the difference between roast beef and pea soup? Answer: Anyone can roast beef but nobody can pee soup!																									
Why did they have to bury George Washington standing up? Answer: Because he could never lie.																									
I didn't like my beard at first. Then it grew on me.																									
What has four wheels and flies? Answer: A garbage truck.																									
"What did the pony say when he had a sore throat? Answer: Sorry, I'm a little horse."																									
"I bet the butcher $50 that he couldn't reach the meat off the top shelf. He said, ""No, the steaks are too high."""																									
Becoming a vegetarian is a huge missed steak.																									
Why can't you tell an egg a joke? Answer: Because it will crack up.																									
Why is gambling illegal in Africa? Answer: Because there are too many cheetahs!																									
Why did the man name his dogs Rolex and Timex? Answer: Because they were watch dogs.																									
"Wanna hear a joke about construction? Answer: Never mind, I'm still working on it."																									
What is the king of all inches? Answer:  The ruler.																									
What do you do with a sick boat? Answer: Take it to the doc.																									
What do you call a famous fish? Answer: A star fish.																									
"A tomato dad, mother, and son are walking in a street. The tomato son falls behind. The big father tomato walks back to the baby tomato, stomps on him, and yells, ""Ketchup!"" "																									
"Wanna hear a joke about a stone? Answer: Never mind, I will just skip that one."																									
Why did the kid throw the butter out the window? Answer: To see the butter-fly!																									
Why did the cow cross the street? Answer: To get to the udder side.																									
Have you heard the joke about the trash can? Answer: It’s garbage!																									
Why do pirates not know the alphabet? Answer: They always get stuck at 'C'.																									
Why can't a bicycle stand up on its own? Answer: Because it's two tired.																									
Why did the house go to the doctor? Answer: It was having window pains.																									
Where do crazy people travel through the forest? Answer: The psycho path.																									
What do you call a Fish without an eye? Answer: A Fsh!																									
What do you call a handcuffed man? Answer: Trustworthy.																									
"What did the fish say when he hit a concrete wall? Answer: ""Dam.”"																									
Why did the dinosaur walk across the road? Answer: Because chickens were not invented yet.																									
When were vowels invented? Answer: When u and i were born.																									
When is it a good time to eat a window? Answer: When it's jammed.																									
Why did the orange use suntan lotion? Answer: He started to peel.																									
"What did the big chimney say to the little chimney? Answer:""You are too young to smoke."""																									
Why did Cinderella get kicked off the baseball team? Answer: Because she ran away from the ball.																									
Why didn't the skeleton cross the road? Answer: Because it had no guts.																									
What did the computer screen say to the keyboard after it went for a ride? Answer: That was a hard drive.																									
Why do chicken coops have two doors? Answer: Because if it had four doors it's be a chicken sedan.																									
How do you know if a restaurant has a clown as a chef? Answer: When the food tastes funny.																									
What do you call a sleeping bull? Answer: A bull-dozer.																									
What did the farmer call the cow that had no milk? Answer: An udder failure.																									
Where do polar bears vote? Answer: The North Pole. 																									
Why are fish so smart? Answer: Because they live in schools.																									
What fish only swims at night? Answer: A starfish!																									
Why did the lion spit out the clown? Answer: Because he tasted funny!																									
Why did the turkey cross the road? Answer: To prove he wasn't chicken!																									
What did the buffalo say to his son when he went away on a trip? Answer: Bison!																									
Why didn't the boy believe the tiger? Answer: He thought it was a lion!																									
What did the computer do at lunchtime? Answer: It had a byte!																									
What is a computer virus? Answer: A terminal illness.																									
Why was the computer cold? Answer: It left it's Windows open.																									
Why did the computer keep sneezing? Answer: It had a virus.																									
Why was there a bug in the computer? Answer: Because it was looking for a byte to eat.																									
What do you get when you cross a computer and a life guard? Answer: A screensaver!																									
What do you call cheese that isn't yours? Answer: Nacho cheese.																									
"Waiter, this food tastes kind of funny? Answer: Then why aren't you laughing."																									
Did you hear the joke about the peanut butter? Answer: I'm not telling you. You might spread it.																									
What did the baby corn say to it's mom? Answer: Where is pop corn.																									
"Waiter, will my pizza be long? Answer: No sir, it will be round."																									
Why did the banana go to the doctor? Answer:  Because it wasn't peeling well! 																									
How do you make a walnut laugh? Answer: Crack it up!																									
In which school do you learn to make ice cream? Answer: Sunday School.																									
What is a pretzel's favorite dance? Answer: The Twist.																									
What are twins favorite fruit? Answer: Pears!																									
What do you give to a sick lemon? Answer: Lemon aid!																									
Why did the lady love to drink hot chocolate? Answer: Because she was a cocoanut.																									
How do you make a milk shake? Answer: Give it a good scare! 																									
What kind of keys do kids like to carry? Answer: Cookies!																									
Where does the Easter bunny get his breakfast? Answer: IHOP! 																									
What do you call a fake stone in Ireland? Answer: A sham rock.																									
Why couldn't the athlete listen to her music? Answer: Because she broke the record.																									
What type of music are balloons scared of? Answer: Pop music!																									
What makes music on your head? Answer: A head band!																									
What part of the turkey is musical? Answer: The drumstick.																									
What has forty feet and sings? Answer: The school choir.																									
What makes pirates such good singers? Answer: They can hit the high C's.																									
How can you tell the ocean is friendly? Answer: It waves.																									
What kind of hair do oceans have? Answer: Wavy!																									
What did Mars say to Saturn? Answer: Give me a ring sometime.																									
What did the big flower say to the small flower? Answer: What's up Bud																									
Where does seaweed go to look for a job? Answer: The kelp wanted section.																									
When is the moon the heaviest? Answer: When it's full!																									
What washes up on very small beaches? Answer: Microwaves!																									
"What did the big flower say to the little flower? Answer: Hey, bud!"																									
Why did the policeman go to the baseball game? Answer: He heard someone had stolen a base!																									
Why did the book join the police? Answer: He wanted to go undercover.																									
Why was there thunder and lightning in the lab? Answer: The scientists were brainstorming.																									
What do lawyers wear to court? Answer: Lawsuits!																									
What do you call a flying police officer? Answer: A helicopter! 																									
Why did the lazy man want a job in a bakery? Answer: So he could loaf around! 																									
What do you call a happy cowboy? Answer: A jolly rancher.																									
What goes up and down but does not move? Answer: Stairs.																									
What did one toilet say to the other? Answer: You look a bit flushed.																									
What did one wall say to the other wall? Answer: I'll meet you at the corner.																									
What gets wetter the more it dries? Answer: A towel.																									
Why do bicycles fall over? Answer: Because they are two-tired.																									
Why was the broom late? Answer: It over swept.																									
"What part of the car is the laziest? Answer: The wheels, because they are always tired."																									
What did the stamp say to the envelope? Answer: Stick with me and we will go places! 																									
Why couldn't the pirate play cards? Answer: Because he was sitting on the deck.																									
What did one elevator say to the other elevator? Answer: I think I'm coming down with something!																									
Why was the belt arrested? Answer: Because it held up some pants!																									
Why was everyone so tired on April 1st? Answer: They had just finished a March of 31 days. 																									
Why can't your nose be 12 inches long? Answer: Because then it would be a foot.																									
What makes the calendar seem so popular? Answer: Because it has a lot of dates.																									
Did you hear about the robbery last night? Answer: Two clothes pins held up a pair of pants.																									
Why did Billy go out with a prune? Answer: Because he couldn't find a date.																									
Why don't traffic lights ever go swimming? Answer: Because they take too long to change.																									
Why did the man run around his bed? Answer: To catch up on his sleep																									
What did the ground say to the earthquake? Answer: You crack me up!																									
Why did nose not want to go to school? Answer: He was tired of getting picked on.																									
How do you get straight A's? Answer: By using a ruler!																									
"What did the pen say to the pencil? Answer: So, what's your point!"																									
When do astronauts eat? Answer: At launch time!																									
What did the pencil sharpener say to the pencil? Answer: Stop going in circles and get to the point.																									
How does the barber cut the moon's hair? Answer: E-clipse it!																									
What happened when the wheel was invented? Answer: It caused a revolution.																									
What is the world's tallest building? Answer: The library because it has the most stories.																									
Why did the clock in the cafeteria run slow? Answer: It always went back four seconds.																									
How is a baseball team similar to a pancake? Answer: They both need a good batter.																									
What's a golfer's favorite letter? Answer: Tee! 																									
What animal is best at hitting a baseball? Answer: A bat!																									
Why did the football coach go to the bank? Answer: He wanted his quarter back.																									
How do football players stay cool during the game? Answer: They stand close to the fans.																									
What is an insect's favorite sport? Answer: Cricket.																									
What is the hardest part about skydiving? Answer: The ground! 																									
What's a tornado's favorite game to play? Answer: Twister.																									
How do you cut the sea in half? Answer: With a sea saw.																									
What did one ocean say to the other ocean? Answer: Nothing they just waved.																									
"What the best thing about Switzerland? Answer: I don’t know, but the flag is a huge plus."																									
What do you call someone elses cheese? Answer: Nacho Cheese.																									
Why does Waldo wear a striped shirt? Answer: Because he doesn't want to be spotted. 																									
Why didn't the skeleton go to the party. Answer: because he has no body to dance with.																									
What kind of beans dont grown in a garden? Answer: Jelly Beans.																									
Why can’t a nose be 12 inches long? Answer: because if it was it would be a foot.																									
Why were the cheerios scared of the man? Answer: Because he was a cereal killer.																									
Why did the baseball player go to jail? Answer: Because he stole second base.																									
What was Benjamin Franklin's reaction to discovering electricity? Answer: He was shocked.																									
What kind of button can’t you find in a sewing shop? Answer: A belly Button.																									
How long does it take to count 4 times infinity? Answer: four-ever.																									
What's an aliens favorite candy? Answer: A Mars bars.																									
Did you hear about the actor that fell through the floor? Answer: It was just a stage he was going through.																									
Why did the cookie complain about feeling sick? Answer: Because he was feeling crummy.																									
Did you hear about the restaurant on the moon. I heard the food is great but there no atmosphere. 																									
Why was the peanut butter angry at the bread. Answer: Because it was loafing around.																									
Why did the string never win a race? Answer: Because it always tied. 																									
What did the tree say to the flower before the race. Answer: I’m rooting for you. 																									
What is the best food to eat when you're scared? Answer: I scream.																									
What did the paper say to the pencil? Answer: Your looking sharp today.																									
Why did the stadium become so hot after the game? Answer: Because all the fans left.																									
What do cowboys like on their salads? Answer: Ranch dressing. 																									
What did the turkey say to the ham? Answer: Nice to meat you. 																									
Who earns a living driving their customers away? Answer: Taxi driver.																									
Whats a race drivers favorite meal? Answer: Fast food.																									
What runs around a football field but never moves? Answer: A fence.																									
A cowboy leaves arrives to a ranch on sunday stays 3 days and leaves of Friday how is this possible? Answer: The horse's name is friday. 																									
What kind of bull doesn't have horns? Answer: A BullFrog. 																									
How are music and fish the same? Answer: Because they both have scales.																									
Why are pigs so bad a soccer? Answer: Because they're always hogging the ball.																									
What is a whale's favorite game? Answer: Swallow the leader. 																									
What do you call a Bear with no ear’s? Answer: B.																									
Why are Horses so negative? Answer: Because they say no to everything.																									
Why count the elephant go into the swimming pool. Answer: Because they were always losing their trunk.																									
Why is it easy to make fun of popsicles? Answer: Because they're suckers for jokes.																									
"What did the whale say to the dolphin? Answer: “Long time no sea."""																									
What to cars and elephants have in common? Answer: They both have trunks.																									
Why did the Seagull fly over the sea? Answer: Because if they flew over the bay they would be Bay-gull’.																									
Why did the Horse keep falling over? Answer: Because their no stable.																									
How do you hit a bee? Answer: With a bee-bee gun.																									
What is the craziest bird in the world? Answer: The coo-coo bird.																									
What do dogs and trees have in common? Answer: they both bark.																									
When do Fireflies get uptight? Answer: When they need to lighten up.																									
Where did the turtle fill up his gas tank? Answer: At the shell station.																									
Why did the cat clean up his mess? Answer: Because it didn’t want to litter.																									
What kind of bugs read the dictionary? Answer: Spelling Bees.																									
What do you call a calf that gets in trouble? Answer: Grounded Beef.																									
What do you get if a cows in a earthquake? Answer: A milkshake.																									
"What's the world's hungriest animal? The turkey, all they do is ""gobble, gobble, gobble""."																									
What do birds do before they work out? Answer: They do their worm-ups.																									
Why do dalmations not like to take baths? Answer:  Because they don't like to be spotless.																									
Why is it easy for elephants to get jobs? Answer: Because they work for peanuts. 																									
What do you give kittens for Christmas? Answer: Santa Claws.																									
																									
																									
																									